be tighter than we've ever been and it's
going to be a great opportunity for us
to be able to respond. Uh that's what
this group has shown they're capable of,
but you give the Panthers credit. Um
they did enough and and they made the
plays to be able to win the football
game. Um and we all can collectively be
able to improve and that's exactly what
we're going to do and we're going to
stay tighter than we've been and this is
a disappointing day, but we're not going
to stay in this moment for long. We'll
look at it. We'll figure out how do we
respond? How do we move forward the
right way? And that's exactly what we're
tasked to do and that's what we will do.
Yeah, just lost track. He just lost
track of the uh of the play clock. It It
felt like it was a pretty quick whistle,
but um that's really as plain as it
gets.
>> Uh you know, I mean, I think it affected
the way that the game was played. You
know, there was three plays offensively
in the third quarter. They possessed it
for a while to start off the you know,
the half and then, you know, you have
that three and out. That sequence was
definitely affected in terms of the
third down where we had a situation that
you know you typically probably are
making that throw and catch but um it
did probably affect us there but for the
most they had to play in it too so it's
not an excuse um they made the plays you
give them the credit and and we'll move
forward the right way guys had so much
success against the run this year off
defense like what led to the struggles
>> you know [snorts] I think we'll go back
and we'll look at it but you know I just
felt like they were getting some good
surges you know we were getting screwed
out of our gaps on a couple different
things where we liked some of the front
mechanics and different calls that we
were in. And we'll go back and we'll
see. But, you know, you give them
credit. They executed well. It seemed
like they were getting some good pushes.
Their backs were falling forward. They
committed to being able to run it even
in some of those third and shorter
windows. And then, you know, the
critical fourth fourth downs, whether it
was the fade or you know, the little
roll pass where they end up leaking uh,
you know, T-Mac out the back door and he
ends up making a big play. Those are,
you know, two fourth down conversions
that were two of their big touchdowns.
They score a defensive touchdown. You
know, there was a lot of things that
were in alignment where hey, you give
them credit. We gave ourselves a chance.
You know, you're down there thinking
you're going to really take the lead.
Felt really good about what we were
going to run um in that particular
situation when we did end up having the
delay. Got a look that we liked and and
we liked the look that we had on the
next third down and unfortunately, you
know, the guy did a good job of being
able to, you know, get it out and and we
turned the ball over.
>> You guys for several weeks have caused a
lot of havoc on quarterbacks. Just I
guess why was it so hard to do that to?
[snorts]
>> We didn't get into a lot of uh you know,
longer distances. is they were fairly
efficient on some of the early downs and
then you know and they they committed
you know we felt like they were probably
going to do that you know that wasn't
something that was a secret thought they
would commit to being able to run the
football and I think they were able to
have their game plan come to life
getting 37 carries off or um you know
however many it was um but it was a lot
and and they were able to control
possession you know cuz really it felt
like you know Matthew and the offense
was doing a good job up and down the
field it was really just the turnovers
you know you have the one punt um in
that you know the the those three plays
that we had in the third quarter, but
you know, this is football. This is, you
know, you got to be able to handle some
tough moments. And our team and the
people in that locker room are made of
the right kind of stuff. We've dealt
with adversity before. We'll deal with
it again and we'll handle it the right
way. And I can't wait to lean in.
Sometimes when uh when things go well,
these can be blessings in disguise if
you use them the right way. You didn't
want it to happen. We came out here with
the expectation to win the football
game. It didn't go down like that for
us. and uh and now we get a chance to be
able to to move forward and and see how
we handle a little bit of a challenge
and it's it's been a while since we felt
this way.
>> You said, you know, humility is a day
away. You said that throughout the week.
>> Yep.
>> Didn't think that we weren't not ready
to go. Didn't think we took this group
lightly. You know, I I I don't believe
that for a second. You know, this is the
NFL. This is too difficult. They did a
great job making plays and they made
plays, you know, and um and we, you
know, it's sometimes you get some, you
know, bounces where it's a tip ball that
goes for an interception when you drive
right down the field. Um, you know,
really wish I had given Matthew a better
play when Jackson ended up kind of
squatting on that out route. Um, and
then, you know, we ended up having an
uncharacteristic, you know, sequence
there towards the latter part when we
get ourselves right down the field.
Matthew and the offense did a great job
of orchestrating a really nice drive.
You're in scoring position. you feel
like you're, you know, going to really
take the lead and win the football game
and and they made a critical play to be
able to force the turnover and and then
they were able to get a first down on a
third and five when thinking you might
get the ball back. So, you know, you
give them credit, their fourth down
execution, forcing turnovers. Um, we
didn't execute the way that we're
capable of. There's certain things that
we can certainly do a better job of
collectively as a coaching staff and we
are all in this together. We're going to
stay tight and uh and we're going to
move forward and and that's all I know
how to do and I know this group feels
the same way. decision to keep two in
the practice window.
>> No, it just it was, you know, it goes
all into, you know, your 48 and and
special teams and all those different
things kind of have factors in that.
>> Okay. All right. Thanks, guys.
Matthew, the turnovers have obviously
not been much of an issue this year for
you or the offense. What do you feel
like was maybe the issue today on the
>> I mean the first one I'm I'm playing
that play the exact same. They did a
nice job getting their hands up tip
ball. I mean that's you know that's the
name of the game. It's you got to you
got to go play aggressive and and that's
fine. second one. Obviously, I can't
leave that ball inside. Guy made a nice
play. Made a bunch of good plays this
year. Um, but can't leave that one
inside and give him seven on that one.
So, that's tough. And then, uh, find a
way to hold on to that last one because
we're in field goal range, you know,
give us a chance to tie that thing up
and let us go play defense. So,
obviously, we're not going to win a
whole lot of games when I turn it over
three times and hasn't been an issue.
And, uh, don't expect it to be moving
forward. just continue to trust my
fundamentals, go out there and play and
and uh you know know that uh I'm doing
all the stuff I can to make sure that I
play at a high level and which didn't
happen for me today.
>> What happened on the game?
>> Yeah, I can't take that. That's that's
that's on nobody but me. I just got to
get that thing off. I thought I had
enough time and I thought I was going to
be snapping it kind of right at, you
know, one zero and um I don't know. I
got to I got to go look at it, but I
thought I thought I did a good enough
job, but I did not. And so that one's
just on me.
you guys tough loss, but do you feel
like you guys still have some momentum?
>> Well, we have all the right guys in
there. That's what I, you know, that's
what I love. Um, you earn momentum in
this league. You know, I mean, you got
to go out there and earn it through the
week. Go out there and play good on
Sunday. I thought we had a great week of
practice. Um, didn't translate to us
playing well today. Um, you know, well
enough to get the win. So, um, you know,
we'll get back to work. And that's what
I feel good about. I feel good about the
guys in our locker room, the coaches in
our locker room that, you know, we're
just going to continue to put the work.
um you know, put the work in and and um
trust the results will come.
>> No, I mean obviously Felton was trying
to move out of there. Um he made a nice
play, but yeah, I mean going from third
and five to third and 10, you know,
makes a big difference on us and uh you
know, I do a better job getting the
first one off.
>> Cool.
>> Sweet. Thank you guys. Appreciate it.
Yeah, we're